if you think meditating journaling
waking up at 5:00 in the morning is
going to make you a better Trader I'm
here to tell you that you are totally
wrong trading for me is like literally
tying my shoes I do the same thing every
single day and no matter if I haven't
slept if I haven't taken a cold shower I
haven't taken a hot shower if I didn't
have my daily breakfast nothing changes
none of this affects my trading because
what really does it for me in my trading
is what I like to call the big four and
in this video I'm going to share with
you what the big four are and how they
made me a successful and most
importantly a consistently profitable
Trader in the markets every single day
and when I really understood this
information and I implemented it into my
day-to-day life every single day my life
changed completely not only did I become
a better Trader but most importantly I
became a better person and as I started
to become a better person this allowed
me to maintain these bigger results that
I was getting in trading week after week
and then month after month so the first
point in the big four is rout routine
routine has to be by far one of the most
important things of the big four they're
all very important but is the first one
and what do I say routine because a lot
of people think that they can just come
to the market whenever they want or
whenever they're free to trade like if
the Market's waiting for them and the
opportunities are just waiting for them
to be free and come to the market that's
not how this works you can't just go
into trading when you have free time off
work or when you decide to put time on
the weekend or let's say you get take a
sneak peek on your phone that's not how
this works you have to have a routine of
when you come into the markets every
single day of every single session so
you're able to see the patterns happen
time and time again having this routine
is what's going to allow you to see the
patterns in the market without this
routine you're not going to be able to
know what happens at the open of New
York session what happens at the close
of New York session what happens at the
beginning of London session what happens
at the close of London session you need
to have a routine that's going to allow
you to be able to look at the market at
these times so you see patterns happen
time and time and time again this
routine is what's going to give you the
ability to now feel confident in your
trading and build a system around that
without you having a routine where
you're going to look at the market at
the same time every single day you're
not going to get the results that you're
destined to get now that is a basic
routine I'm not saying you have to
meditate I'm not saying you have to take
a shower I'm not saying you have to read
five pages I personally thank God that
is a marketing gimmick I've never done
that in my life from the moment I wake
up from my bed I can wake up at 8:30 in
the morning I'm in my computer desk at
8:45 waiting for 9:00 a.m. that's it
I'll be scrolling through Instagram just
kind of wasting time until it becomes 9:
and that's how I get into the market I
don't have to clear my mind I don't have
to read a book of trading in the zone I
don't have to do any of that stuff so
once you have a trading plan and a
routine the market patterns are going to
be there I think all of that stuff is
just a facade but you know it works for
some people for me I personally just
need to be in front of the markets every
single day at the same time cuz the
market is going to give me the pattern
every single day at the same time but
routine would be useless without my
second point which is going to be
patience and patience is a very big
factor because pulling out to the market
every single day at the same time with
this routine it's you're not going to
get results right away because it's
going to take you time to see the
patterns it's going to take you time to
get used to this routine and you know
doing it every single day and it's going
to take you time for even for it to
become your new normal so when you add
patience to a routine it almost becomes
second nature it's like tying your shoes
the first example that I gave in this
video for me getting into the markets
every single day it's literally like
waking up and brushing my teeth and
putting on my shoes it's the same thing
every single day I do it subconsciously
I do it so subconsciously that I even do
it on the weekends so if you implement
patience with your routine now you're
destined to have success on the long run
and you add this to your personal life
and your personal life ends up getting
better because you realize that you need
to have a routine in life and and things
simply take time good things take time
it's just the reality of the situation
and now that you understand patience
this leads me to my third point which
goes in line with what I was just
mentioning and that is respect you need
to have respect to yourself you have to
understand you have to be there every
single day at the routine you have to
understand that this takes time now when
you don't have results for 6 months
after doing the same thing every single
day but you're just a little bit better
every single time need to respect
yourself and your time and appreciate
the time that you have put into it and
just because 6 months have gone by and
you you're not a millionaire you don't
have a Lambo yet don't just give up
don't just throw in the rag and say
that's it you need to respect yourself
you need to respect the craft that it
takes to become a successful Trader you
need to respect the habits and the
routines that you need to build as your
own person the person that you go into
trading is not the same person that
you're going to be when you get out of
ating and you need to respect that it's
the simple truth L said right now you
want to go into the military you are not
the same person when you go into the
military as when you get out I know it's
for personal experience I applied to Roc
and I had a mindset of what it was going
to be and as as I was in drtc training I
realized the reality of the situation
it's not what it is and I came out a
completely different person respecting
soldiers and respecting my troops by a
million per. and this same thing comes
into trading you you need to respect the
rules and need to respect the morals
that you need to have when it comes to
trading having risk management staying
true to your trading plan only risking a
certain percentage of your account being
patient with your take profit and stop-
loss getting hit waiting for entry sign
these are all things that you need to
respect in trading along with your
patience and your routine so you become
a profitable Trader the respect that you
give yourself are the results you're
going to get yourself and finally my
fourth and obviously most important
point and what is going to give you the
biggest results on the long run that is
going to be consistency without
consistency none of this would be
possible I am here today because I wake
up every single day and I apply my
routine I wake up every single day and
I'm patient for my trade setup I wake up
every single day and I respect my
trading plan and myself s my time
everything but that is because I am
consistent I do it every single day from
the moment that I learned about Forex
Trading or day trading as a whole late
2018 early 2019 there hasn't been one
single day except the weekends that I
have not looked at the markets not one
single day I have been on top of this
craft every single day because to me
this isn't a job I love what I do I love
getting into the markets and just simply
waiting there for a pattern to happen
and I can literally predict what the
pattern is going to do because I've seen
it happen time and time again and that
gives me a Feeling of satisfaction
because my consistency is paying off
without consistency I won't see the
patterns without consistency I won't
learn the mistakes without consistency I
won't be able to implement the mistakes
that I have been experienced in the
market without consistency I won't be
able to grow without consistency nothing
is possible and with consistency all of
those late nights all of those endless
hours all of those losses become worth
it but the day you throw in the rag is a
day that you are than a loser a winner
is somebody that simply didn't stop
trying a loser is somebody that stopped
trying and took the L consistency is
what carries the big four in order for
you to be a successful Trader and have
consistent profits in the markets and I
can almost guarantee you if you
implement these four habits along with
my profitable set F strategy your
trading results would change by 100%
students using my set set and forget
strategy are making anywhere from $1,000
to
$1,500 a week as a beginner set and
forget strategy now if you don't know
what set and forget is just click the
link in the description below and I
explain all about what my set forget
strategy is and how you can have those
results too but this s forget trading
plan doesn't just stop there we have a
weekly call every single week where I
give you the markets and most
importantly we talk about our emotions
we talk about psychology I have a whole
psychology section within the set and
forget strategy so you can learn how to
implement these four habits when you're
having a bad week when you're having a
winning week when you're having a slow
week all of these things are things that
happen in the market and it affects
every single Trader differently little
did you guys know that winning might
affect somebody more than losing because
they don't know how to handle their wins
so if you want to become a student and
learn how to make anywhere from ,000 to
$1,500 a week as a beginner Center
forget Trader just click the link in the
description below and I'll explain to
you what the center forget strategy is
and how you can make these profits
within your first 3 months of using the
set of forget strategy hope you guys
found this video useful and I'll see you
guys in the next video